Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Activism, 1973-2000, Undated; 1; 11.35 cubic ft.
  - National March on Washington, 1987, 1979-1989, Undated; 1.4; 2.3 cubic ft.
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Fundraising and Finances, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 76)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Handbook, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Mailings, 1987; Undated (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Maps, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Medical Concerns, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Meetings, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Notes, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Participant Evaluations, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Participant Information, 1987 (Oversized 4, Folder 18)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Participants and Contacts, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Permits, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Photographs, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Planning, Legal Pads, 1987 (Oversized 4, Folder 19)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Planning, Legal Pads, 1987 (Oversized 4, Folder 20)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Press Coverage, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Regional Planning, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Schedules, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Speeches, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Staff Searches, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 15)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Training Sessions, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 16)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Washington Landmarks, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 17)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Writings, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 19)
    - Demands and Goals, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 20)
    - Documentary of March on Washington, C.D., The Ritual of Civil Disobedience, directed by Sorrell Hays (24 min), 1987 (Vhs 4)
    - Endorsements, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 21)
    - Fundraising and Finances, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 22)
    - Gay and Lesbian Electronic Access Network, Undated (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 23)
    - Guidebook, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 24)
    - JEB (Joan E. Biren), 1987; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 25)
    - Lesbian Rights Lobby Kit, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 26)
    - Lobby Day, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 27)
    - Mailings and Invitations, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 28)
    - Maps, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 29)
    - Meetings, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 30)
    - Memoranda, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 31)
    - Merchandising, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 32)
    - NAMES Project/AIDS Memorial Quilt, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 33)
    - Name tag - Press Pass for Lesbian Nation, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 34)
    - Name tag - Michelle Crone, Civil Disobedience Chairperson, 1987 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 35)
    - National Office of the March on Washington, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 36)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 37)
    - National Steering Committee, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 38)
    - Never Forget/Harvey Milk Ceremony, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 39)
    - Notes, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 40)
    - Office Scene, mounted photograph, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 41)
    - Organizing Committee, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 42)
    - Organizing Conference, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 43)
    - Organizing Kit, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 44)
    - "Out and Outraged," sheet music, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 45)
    - Participants and Delegations, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 46)
    - Permit, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 47)
    - Photographs, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 48)
    - Plastic Basket labeled March on Washington, Undated (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Post-March Material, 1987-1989 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 49)
    - Post-March organizing and notes, 1987; 1988 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 50)
    - Press Coverage, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 51)
    - Press Coverage, 1986; 1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
    - Press Coverage, 1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
    - Press Coverage, 1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
    - Press Coverage, 1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
    - Press Coverage, 1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
    - Press Coverage, 1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
    - Press Coverage, 1987; 1988 (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
    - Press Coverage, February, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 52)
    - Press Coverage, April, May, and June, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 53)
    - Press Coverage, July, August, and September, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 54)
    - Press Coverage, October-December, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 55)
    - Press Coverage, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 56)
    - Press coverage - Names Quilt, 1989 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 57)
    - Proposals and Resolutions, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 58)
    - Publicity, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 59)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 5)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 6)
    - Publicity and posters, 1987 (Oversized 2, Folder 7)
    - Regional Planning, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 60)
    - Schedules of Events, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 61)
    - S/M-Leather Contingent, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 62)
    - Small stuffed bear with pin - Out and Outraged, For Love, Life & Liberation, Lesbian/Gay Civil Disobedience, 1987 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Steering Committee, Regional Representatives, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 63)
    - T-shirt - March on Washington for Lesbian & Gay Civil Rights, 1987 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - T-shirt - Staff, National March on Washington for Lesbian & Gay Rights, 1987 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - T-shirt - Staff, National March on Washington for Lesbian & Gay Rights, 1987 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Technical Production, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 64)
    - Travel and Accommodation, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 65)
    - The Wedding/Couples, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 66)
    - Writings, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 67)
  - National March on Washington, 1993, 1987-1994, Undated; 1.5; 2.6 cubic ft.
    Alphabetical by subject.
    This subseries includes administrative records from Michelle Crone's service on the Interim Coordinating Committee and the Executive Committee for the 1993 March on Washington, as well as her job as March Coordinator for the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force. This includes handwritten meeting notes, minutes, correspondence, formal and informal reports, political literature, fliers and other publications, newspaper clippings, ephemera, permits, schedules, information on performers and ephemera. Michelle Crone also collected newspaper clippings and articles pertaining to the march which can be found in the “Press Coverage” folders.
    - Action Kit: Fight the Right, 1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 68)
    - AIDS/People with AIDS, 1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 69)
    - Anthem, 1992 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 70)
    - Buttons - 1993 National March on Washington (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Artwork, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 71)
    - Bisexuality, 1989; 1991; 1992; Undated (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 72)
    - Business Cards, ca. 1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 73)
    - Civil Disobedience, ca. 1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 74)
    - Commemorative Video for the 1993 March on Washington for Gay, Lesbian and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation, In The Life Productions (Vhs 5)
    - The Committee for the March on Washington, Inc., 1992; 1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 75)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 76)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 77)
    - Demands and Platforms, 1992-1993 (Box 4 (1-Activism), Folder 78)
    - "Demonstrating in the District of Columbia" Handbook, 1991 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - Endorsements, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Melissa Etheridge (with photographs), ca. 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee By Laws, Log Cabin, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Membership, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee Planning Notes, ca. 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee Proposals, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - Finances, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Fundraising, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Gay and Lesbian Histories Exhibit, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - Interim Coordinating Committee (ICC) with photographs, 1991-1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 15)
    - JEB: Joan E. Biren, ca. 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 16)
    - The Lesbian and Gay Bands of America, March on Washington 1993, March and Concert Excerpts (Vhs 6)
    - Mailings, 1990; 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 17)
    - Maps, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 18)
    - Medical Committee, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 19)
    - Medical Committee, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 20)
    - Meetings, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 21)
    - Memoranda, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 22)
    - Metrocard, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 23)
    - Merchandising, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 24)
    - The Names Project/New York Memorial Quilt, 1987; 1988; 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 25)
    - Name tag - Michelle Crone, Executive Committee, the 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Name tag - National Executive Committee, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 26)
    - Name tag - National Steering Committee Meeting, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 27)
    - Name tag - Stage 2, 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 28)
    - National Organization for Woman, Inc. (NOW), 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 29)
    - National Organizing Facilitator Search, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 30)
    - National Steering Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 31)
    - Newsletters and Mailings, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 32)
    - Notes, ca. 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 33)
    - Organizing Kit, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 34)
    - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays, Inc. (P-FLAG), 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 35)
    - Participants and Delegations, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 36)
    - People with Disabilities, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 37)
    - Performers, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 38)
    - Performers: Barbara Lee Supeno, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 39)
    - Performers: Crazy Eights Management, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 40)
    - Performers: Disappear Fear, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 41)
    - Performers: Girls in the Nose, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 42)
    - Performers: Maile Klein & Marina Hodgini, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 43)
    - Performers: Lesbian and Gay Bands of America, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 44)
    - Performers: Pandy Division, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 45)
    - Performers: Penny Arcade, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 46)
    - Performers: Phrane, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 47)
    - Performers: Rhythm Express, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 48)
    - Performers: River Sui, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 49)
    - Performers: RuPaul, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 50)
    - Performers: Fred Small, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 51)
    - Performers: Doug Stevens and the Outband, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 52)
    - Performers: Lynn E. Thomas, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 53)
    - Performers: Suzanne Westenhoefer, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 54)
    - Performers: Tom Wilson Weinberg, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 55)
    - Performers: Winkte and Crazy Sacred Dogs, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 56)
    - Permits/National Park Service, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 57)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 58)
    - Photographs, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 59)
    - Political Literature, ca. 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 60)
    - Post-March Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 61)
    - Post-March Materials, 1994; Undated (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 62)
    - Posters (20in by 24in), 1993 (Oversized 5, Folder 1)
    - Posters - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force March on Washington, 1993 (Oversized 5, Folder 2)
    - Posters - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, "Fight Back," March on Washington, 1993 (Oversized 5, Folder 5)
    - "Prelude to Victory" The 1993 March on Washington Video, Girard Video (Vhs 7)
    - Press Coverage, 1991; 1992 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 63)
    - Press Coverage, 1992; 1993 (Oversized 2, Folder 8)
    - Press Coverage, 1992; 1993 (Oversized 2, Folder 9)
    - Press Coverage, 1993 (Oversized 2, Folder 10)
    - Press Coverage, 1993 (Oversized 2, Folder 11)
    - Press Coverage, 1993 (Oversized 2, Folder 12)
    - Press Coverage, January, February and March, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 64)
    - Press Coverage, April, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 65)
    - Press Coverage, May and June, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 66)
    - Press Coverage, July and August, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 67)
    - Press Coverage, September, October, November, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 68)
    - Press Coverage, December and later, 1993; 1994; Undated (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 69)
    - Press Packets, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 70)
    - Press Pass, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 71)
    - Press Releases, 1991-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 72)
    - Program Guides, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 73)
    - Proposals and Resolutions, 1991-1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 74)
    - Publicity, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 75)
    - Publicity and posters, 1993 (Oversized 2, Folder 13)
    - Rainbow Bracelet - 1993 March on Washington (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - Regional Planning, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 76)
    - Related Events, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 77)
    - Schedules of Events, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 78)
    - Security, 1993 (Box 5 (1-Activism), Folder 79)
    - "A Simple Matter of Justice: Post-March Press Clippings", 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - SM/Leather/Fetish Contingent, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Small stuffed doll with pin on face - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force, A Simple Matter of Justice, March on Washington, 1993 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Andrew Stein: New York City Council President, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - Stickers, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - T-shirt - 1993 National March on Washington Logistics Team (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - T-shirt - 1993 National March on Washington Michelle Crone Executive Committee (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - T-shirt - A Simple Matter of Justice, 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - T-shirt - Fight Back, National Gay & Lesbian Task Force March on Washington, 1993 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - T-shirt - It's a Simple Matter of Justice, National Gay & Lesbian Task Force March on Washington, 1993 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - T-shirt - It's a Simple Matter of Justice, National Gay & Lesbian Task Force March on Washington, 1993 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - T-shirt - It's a Simple Matter of Justice, National Gay & Lesbian Task Force March on Washington, 1993 (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - T-shirt - Marshall, 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - T-shirt - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force, A Simple Matter of Justice, March on Washington (white), 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - T-shirt - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force, A Simple Matter of Justice, March on Washington (white), 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - T-shirt - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force, A Simple Matter of Justice, March on Washington (grey), 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - T-shirt - Security, 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - T-shirt - Security, 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - T-shirt - Security, 1993 (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - T-shirt - The 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay, and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation (Box 23 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - Technical Production, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Telephone Messages, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Tickets to Events, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - Timelines, 1991-1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Transgender, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Travel and Accommodations, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - Robin Tyler, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Washington Support Committee, 1992 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Weather, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - The Wedding, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - Work Committees, ca. 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 15)
    - Writings, 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 16)
  - Seneca Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice (1983-1988), 1982-1991, Undated; 1.6; 2.6 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains the records from the Seneca Women’s Peace Encampment in Romulus, New York. This includes political literature, correspondence, financial records, mailings, ephemera, meeting minutes, and grant proposals. The series also includes registration forms for the entire encampment for 1983. Also present is information on nuclear energy and radiation collected by Michelle Crone in respect to the goals of the encampment.
    - "Action Info" Forms, 1983 (Oversized 4, Folder 21)
    - Action Records, 1983; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Actions and Rallies, 1982-1986; 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - Activism/Peace Resources, 1974; 1980-1983; 1985-1988; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Artwork, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Banner - Womyn Resist III, Women's Peace Camps International (72in by 92in, drawn on bedsheet), Undated (Box 25 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - Banner - Seneca Women's Peace Camp, sewn depiction of women with peace sign, women symbol, poetry, writings, buttons (42in by 82in, sewn on bedsheet), Undated (Box 25 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Cassette tape - Woman's Peace Encampment "Being Ourselves" Ithaca Feminist Radio, 1991 (Cassette 2)
    - Children in Crisis, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - Contact Lists, 1983; 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Contents of Notebook, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1988; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - Donations coffee can with buttons, ca. 1984 (Box 30 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Drawing of two Native Americans (17in by 21in), Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 4)
    - Dykes Opposed to Nuclear Technology, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - E.L.F. Waves, E.E.G. Entrainment, Psychotronic Warfare & Welfare, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 15)
    - EMR/"Zapping", 1965; 1980; 1982; 1983; 1985-1989 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 16)
    - EMR/"Zapping", Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 17)
    - Field Journal, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 18)
    - Finances, 1983; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 19)
    - Fundraising, 1983; 1984; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 20)
    - Gallery 345/Art for Social Change, Inc., 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 21)
    - Garlick's Mini-Mart, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 22)
    - Grant Proposals, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 23)
    - Grant Proposals, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 24)
    - Grant Proposals, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 25)
    - Grant Proposals, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 26)
    - Hat with buttons - Sonia Johnson, Citizens Party, Women's Encampment for Peace and Justice, Undated (Box 25 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - Legal Fund, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 27)
    - Life at Camp, Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 28)
    - Mailings, 1983-1988; 1997; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 29)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 30)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 31)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 32)
    - Microwave News, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 33)
    - Microwave News, 1988; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 34)
    - Memoranda, 1989 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 35)
    - News clippings, 1983-1984; 1987; 1989; 1992; 1993 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 36)
    - Newsletters, 1986; Undated (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 37)
    - No trespassing poster = "Nuclear Free Zone, Women's Land", 1984 (Oversized 2, Folder 19)
    - Non-Registration Forms - A, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 38)
    - Non-Registration Forms - B, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 39)
    - Non-Registration Forms - B, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 40)
    - Non-Registration Forms - B, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 41)
    - Non-Registration Forms - C, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 42)
    - Non-Registration Forms - C, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 43)
    - Non-Registration Forms - D, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 44)
    - Non-Registration Forms - D-E, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 45)
    - Non-Registration Forms - F, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 46)
    - Non-Registration Forms - G, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 47)
    - Non-Registration Forms - G-H, 1983 (Box 6 (1-Activism), Folder 48)
    - Non-Registration Forms - H, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - Non-Registration Forms - I-J, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - Non-Registration Forms - K, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - Non-Registration Forms - L, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - Non-Registration Forms - M, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Non-Registration Forms - M, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Non-Registration Forms - N-O, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - Non-Registration Forms - P-Q, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Non-Registration Forms - R, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Non-Registration Forms - R, 1983 (Box 7 (1-Activism), Folder 10)